[ ominous music ]
[ knife slices ]
[ knife slicing ]
- [ knife slices ] - [ water splashing ]
[ knife slices ]
[ knife slicing ]
- [ knife slicing ] - [ Halloween theme music ]
[ sirens wailing ]
[ knife slices ]
[ tires screeching ]
[ Rachel screaming ]
[ body thudding ]
[ Rachel ] Die , you son of a bitch !
- [ engine roaring ] - [ tires screeching ]
[ body thuds ]
- [ body thuds ] - [ wood thudding ]
[ insects chirping ]
[ Rachel ] Jamie , I want you to stay in the car .
- [ sirens wailing ] - [ truck door clicks ]
[ gentle ominous music ]
[ man ] Jamie ! Get away !
Don 't touch him , Jamie !
[ ominous music ]
[ officer ] That 's him . Don 't hit the girl .
- Careful . - Get down !
[ gun fires ]
[ guns firing ]
[ boards crashing ]
[ gun clicks ]
[ ominous music ]
[ man ] I don 't understand this , what happened ?
[ woman ] That 's it .
[ water dripping ]
[ man speaking indistinctly ]
- [ man ] Everyone okay ? - [ woman ] Yeah .
[ indistinct chattering ]
[ guns clicking ]
[ officer ] Do it . Stand back .
[ fuse hissing ]
[ explosion booming ]
[ Halloween theme music ]
[ water splashing ]
[ insects chirping ]
[ bird chattering ]
Quiet , Tookie .
Be quiet .
[ ominous music ]
- [ branch snaps ] - [ bird squawks ]
[ bird chattering ]
[ bird squawks ]
[ door creaking ]
[ leaves rustling ]
[ bird chattering ]
There 's nothing out there , Tookie .
[ door bangs ]
- [ suspenseful music ] - [ gasps ]
[ body thuds ]
[ bird chattering ]
[ brooding music ]
[ ominous music ]
- [ thunder crashing ] - [ rain pattering ]
[ thunder rumbling ]
[ thunder crashing ]
[ ominous music ]
[ Jamie gasping ] No .
No , no , no !
[ Darlene ] Come on , Jamie .
Your bath is ready .
[ water splashing ]
[ Jamie screaming ] Mom !
[ gasping ]
- [ Darlene screaming ] - [ Halloween theme music ]
[ Jamie screaming ]
Jamie ! [ screams ]
- [ gasping , screaming silently ] - [ thunder crashing ]
It 's all right , it 's all right , darling .
Oh , oh , Jamie .
[ monitor beeping ]
Jamie , Jamie , it 's just another one
of your nightmares , that 's all .
Oh , oh .
Oh , darling , look at me , look at me .
Do you want me to call your Mom ?
- [ screaming silently ] - Huh ? Oh .
Oh , Jamie , Jamie .
[ ominous music ]
[ Jamie gasps ]
[ bird chattering ]
[ Jamie gasping ]
[ thunder crashing ]
[ bird squawks ]
I 'll call the doctor .
[ panting ]
[ bird chattering ]
[ suspenseful music ]
[ bird squawks ]
[ Jamie panting ]
[ thunder crashing ]
[ chalk squeaking ]
[ bird squawks ]
[ thunder crashing ]
- [ muffled grunt ] - [ neck snaps ]
[ body thuds ]
[ Jamie gasping ]
- [ fist thudding ] - [ man groans ]
Oh , Jamie .
Oh , Jamie , Jamie .
Doctor !
[ thunder crashing ]
Get a gurney , somebody !
Come on . Okay , yeah , ready .
- Go , go ! - Jamie , breathe .
Breathe , Jamie .
Jamie , breathe .
- Breathe , Jamie . - Prep ER .
- Tracheotomy , go ! - No !
Jamie , Jamie , Jamie , Jamie .
- [ man ] All right , down . - [ doctor ] There you go .
Easy , easy , easy does it .
- [ man ] You got her up there ? - [ doctor ] Yeah , steady , steady .
[ Jamie gasping ]
[ doctor ] She needs oxygen .
All right , unstrap her .
[ Jamie gasping ]
All right .
[ thunder rumbling ]
[ Loomis ] No !
- No ! - What are you doing ?
- [ Loomis ] Leave her ! - [ doctor ] This girl is dying .
I have to open her trachea , for God 's sake .
She will stabilize .
[ doctor ] She 's dying !
[ Loomis ] No .
[ brooding music ]
[ thunder rumbling ]
[ Loomis ] You see ?
I see you still want this girl dead .
She has something to tell us .
[ birds chirping ]
[ door creaking ]
[ door bangs ]
Hey there , funny face .
What ?
Thank you .
Hey , hey , open up !
Mm , mm !
- [ faintly ] Max . Max . - [ dog barks ]
- [ Tina ] Hi . - They don 't allow Max in here .
Get in there , Max .
- Tina . - You know what they can do
if they can 't take a joke .
She doesn 't even remember .
- [ Max whining ] - [ Tina ] Is she really better ?
Hey , hey , hey , hey ! [ laughs ]
Mmm !
Give me some of this action , baby .
[ mouthing words ]
What ?
Uh-huh .
Ah , I wonder what Rachel 's hiding behind door number three .
Ba-bom-ba-da !
Bom-ba-ba-da-bom-ba-bom-ba-da !
- Ta-da ! - [ Tina yells ]
Bom-ba-da-ba-bom-ba-da-ba-ba !
Bom-ba-da-ba-ba-ba-ba !
Bom-ba-da !
- It 's gonna look so good . - Bom-ba-da !
Bom-ba-da-bom-ba-da-bom-ba-dah !
- I 'm glad you like it . - Billy is going to have to fight off - -
- Billy 's gonna freak . - ... a lot of boys !
- [ door bangs ] - [ dog barking ]
[ Loomis ] What is going on here ?
[ Rachel laughs ]
[ Tina ] Gee , sorry .
Come on , Max , come here .
Bye , sweetie , love you .
[ whispers ] Sorry .
I 'll be back in two days , okay ?
Mom and Dad send their love .
Come here .
- [ glass shattering ] - [ suspenseful music ]
[ Jamie gasps ]
[ dog barking ]
[ tires squealing ]
[ glass crashing ]
[ paper rustling ]
[ ominous music ]
[ sighs ] How could they ?
When are they gonna realize that she is not him ?
She 's just a child .
They know that Michael Myers is her uncle
and that she attacked her stepmother .
That 's why they fear her , especially on Halloween .
I never should 've let my parents talk me into leaving .
I don 't know what I was thinking .
You are afraid .
I am not .
You 're afraid the whole thing might start to happen again .
There 's nothing wrong with being afraid .
And I suppose there 's nothing wrong
with just leaving my little stepsister here alone .
You can telephone her from the cabin .
She 'll be properly looked after .
Then why do I still feel guilty ?
- [ rock music ] - I 'm worried about Jamie .
So , stick around .
I already promised my parents .
Promises were made to be broken , babe .
I don 't know .
The farm 's parties always rock .
- Think about it . - Okay .
- I gotta jet . Bye . - [ Rachel ] Bye .
- [ dog barking ] - [ Tina ] I 'll be back with the outfits .
[ Rachel ] See you , Tina .
- [ dog barks ] - Max !
[ ominous music ]
Max , what is it ?
Come on , Max .
Oh , come on .
[ heavy breathing ]
[ upbeat music ]
♪ When we first met up ♪
♪ We started off all wrong ♪
♪ And the pace was just too fast ♪
- ♪ For hanging on ♪ - [ heavy breathing ]
[ Rachel ] Come on , Max .
♪ Gotta go , Romeo ♪
Come on . Yes , Max .
♪ Pack up your things , head back out the window ♪
♪ I 'm looking around for a new Romeo ♪
- [ ominous music ] - [ heavy breathing ]
- [ girl ] Here , you want this ? - [ boy ] That 's mine .
[ indistinct chattering ]
[ girl 2 ] Oh , thank you .
- [ birds chirping ] - [ heavy breathing ]
- [ ominous music ] - [ indistinct chattering ]
- [ boy 2 ] I want the scissors . - [ boy 3 ] That 's mine .
[ indistinct chattering ]
[ dog barking ]
- [ heavy breathing ] - [ dog barking ]
Shut up , Max .
[ dog barking ]
- [ Jamie panting ] - [ indistinct chattering ]
[ indistinct chattering ]
[ dog barking ]
[ girl ] ] Jamie .
Jamie .
[ Jamie gasping ]
[ boy ] Max ?
[ indistinct chattering ]
- [ water splashing ] - [ phone ringing ]
All right .
[ sighs ] Hold on a minute .
[ heavy breathing ]
All right .
[ sighs ] I 'm coming .
Hello .
Oh , are you all right ?
Yeah , I 'm fine . I was just in the shower .
Is ... is Max all right ?
[ sighs ] Max is having fun .
He 's been barking at a cat all morning .
- Go and check him . - Well , why ?
Go and check him now !
All right . [ scoffs ]
All right . Hold on , I have to go downstairs .
Oh , brother .
[ indistinct chattering ]
- [ birds chirping ] - [ heavy breathing ]
[ suspenseful music ]
[ door creaking ]
- [ Rachel shouts over phone ] - [ phone clanging ]
Rachel ?
[ indistinct chattering ]
[ Rachel over phone ] Dr. Loomis .
Max is gone .
Listen to me .
Drop the phone , go to the nearest store ,
get out of the house . Quickly , now , go on !
[ phone thuds ]
[ ominous music ]
[ heavy breathing ]
[ Rachel ] Mr. Cornish .
[ Rachel panting ]
- [ police radio chattering ] - [ indistinct chattering ]
[ playful music ]
- All clear . - Nothing above , nothing below .
[ scoffs ] Well , what about Max ?
A doby , right ?
[ man ] There he is .
This is not happening to me .
Max .
- Max , what have you done ? - [ Max whining ]
I 'm so embarrassed .
Hey , it 's what we 're here for .
- Rescue cats . - Find dogs .
- That 's our job . - And we love it .
[ playful music ]
[ Rachel over phone ] Bye , sweetie . I love you .
You be a good girl .
Bye .
[ phone clicks ]
So she was perfectly all right .
Come on , Billy .
I think Jamie needs to get some rest .
Jamie , are you okay ?
[ Loomis ] Come on .
[ door bangs ]
You sense something , don 't you ?
Tell me .
Tell me what you know !
Here , write , write , write !
Write what you know .
Jamie , please !
Please .
[ hair dryer whirring ]
[ birds chirping ]
[ heavy breathing ]
[ ominous music ]
Yeah .
Hmm .
- [ dog barking ] - [ sighs ]
Max .
[ buzzes lips ]
[ dog barking ]
[ suspenseful music ]
Max .
[ dog barking ]
[ glass shatters ]
- [ ominous music ] - [ dog barking ]
[ door creaking ]
[ dog barking ]
[ gentle pensive music ]
[ suspenseful music ]
[ door creaking ]
- No ! [ screaming ] - [ Halloween theme music ]
[ Jamie gasping ]
The dictataline should have taken effect by now .
Another dose might stop her heart .
She was shaking .
Her whole body was shaking .
Every time a little girl twitches ,
I 'm supposed to call out the National Guard .
How many people did he kill last year ?
Have you forgotten ... your own daughter ?
- I don 't - - - No , of course you don 't forget !
How could you ?
But you never looked into his face , did you ?
You never saw his eyes .
You never saw that , that nothing .
No expression , blank , huh .
My memory goes back 12 years ,
to the night when I offered my - -
I 'm gonna show you , show you something .
Look , look , look at this .
Look at that .
I prayed that he would burn in hell ,
but in my heart I knew that hell would not have him .
Sheriff ?
They want you down at the cemetery .
[ ominous music ]
[ birds chirping ]
- [ doorknob jiggling ] - [ dog barking ]
- [ doorbell ringing ] - [ Tina ] Rach .
- [ ominous music ] - [ dog barking ]
[ dog barking ]
Maxie !
[ kissing noises ]
[ dog barking ]
Chill out , Max .
I 'll get you water in a second .
[ door creaking ]
Rach ?
Rachel ?
- [ static hissing ] - [ heavy breathing ]
Rachel , Rachel .
Rachel , I got you a present .
Rachel .
[ needle scratches ]
Rachel ?
[ dog barking ]
- Rachel . - [ brooding rock music ]
[ Tina giggling ]
[ ominous music ]
Rachel ?
[ brooding rock music ]
Gonna miss you , baby !
[ ominous music ]
[ wind blowing ]
[ bag thuds ]
[ gentle pensive music ]
[ Tina sighs ]
- [ doorbell ringing ] - [ Tina gasps ]
- [ dog barking ] - [ Tina giggles ]
Sammy ?
[ door creaking ]
[ birds chirping ]
- [ Sam ] Boo ! - [ both yelping ]
- [ Sam laughing ] - [ Tina ] Hi !
It 's Halloween , right ?
Can you believe we have this whole house
to ourselves for the weekend ?
But , Tina , that 's what you 've said before , remember ?
Oh , Sammy , are all your circuits on hold or what ?
[ dog barking ]
[ Tina laughing ]
Hey , Tina , I thought Rachel was sticking around .
Oh , I did , too .
But I guess she decided to go out to the country with her parents .
Oh , Max , shut your canine trap !
What if my mom calls
and finds out Rachel is not here with us , huh ?
- [ heavy breathing ] - Just joking ! [ laughs ]
[ bird squawking ]
[ ominous music ]
[ Jamie gasping ]
Sammy , why don 't you bag Spitz tonight ?
- I couldn 't do that . - Oh , sure , you could .
- Oh , no , I can 't . - Oh , come on .
Ooh , you 're blushing ! [ giggles ]
Come on .
Come on , you can 't hide anything from me .
- Come on . - This may be it .
- [ chuckles ] - It ?
[ ominous music ]
[ Tina ] What are you saying ?
God , I can 't talk to you about this .
Oh , come on , come on .
I mean , you 're planning something .
I mean , what are we talking here , like , candles and ,
and , uh , a sensual massage and leopard sheets ?
Satin .
- Satin sheets ? - They 're Rachel 's !
[ both laughing ]
Yeah , I just flipped my skirt !
What do you want me to do ? What can I do , what can I do ?
I mean , do you want to make up signals or something ?
- Tina , no . - [ giggles ] What ?
Come on , you guys can have the house to yourselves .
It 's cool .
Mikey and I like it in the car .
[ both laughing ]
Aw , honey , don 't worry about it .
- [ gasping ] - [ Sam ] I 'm not worried .
I 've just been in a weird mood all day .
Well , everybody in this town is in a weird mood .
They should ban Halloween in this town .
[ both laughing ]
[ Tina ] Michael ?
What ?
♪ Anything for money ♪
♪ Almost nothing I won 't do ♪
- ♪ I 'll do anything ♪ - [ Tina ] Hi .
♪ For money ♪
Hey , you 're just in time to give us a ride .
♪ ... can I do for you ♪
Come on , Sammy . Sorry about last weekend .
[ Sam scoffs ]
Aren 't you , Mike ?
No . [ laughs ]
See ?
Tina , I thought you wanted to see Jamie .
Look , you 're killing me , babe , okay ?
- Would you just get in ? - [ scoffs ]
We could go later , right , Mikey ?
Right ?
♪ Almost nothing I won 't do ♪
- [ car engine revving ] - [ ominous music ]
♪ Anything for money ♪
[ car engine roaring ]
♪ What can I do for you ♪
- [ monitor beeping ] - [ Jamie grunting ]
- [ tires screeching ] - [ ominous music ]
[ grunting ]
- [ suspenseful music ] - [ Jamie gasps ]
[ ominous music ]
[ Jamie groans ]
[ Halloween theme music ]
[ Jamie whimpering ]
[ suspenseful music ]
- [ door rattling ] - [ panting ]
- [ Jamie cries ] - [ door rattling ]
[ air hissing ]
- [ machine whirring ] - [ sheets rustling ]
[ sheets ripping ]
- [ door bangs ] - [ air hissing ]
[ Jamie whimpering ]
[ light clanging ]
It 's all right .
What are you doing down here ?
Come on , come on .
- It 's okay . - There you are .
We 've been looking all over for you .
Come to me , baby . Come on .
What happened ?
Was it one of your dreams again ?
Huh , huh ?
Okay , come on .
[ door bangs ]
You gotta help me , Jamie .
You gotta help me to find him .
We both know he 's alive , but you know where he is !
Why ?
Why are you protecting him ?
- Why ? - [ objects clattering ]
What about your stepmother , Jamie ?
You love her , don 't you ? He made you stab her .
[ Jamie crying ]
You can 't hide from him .
He 'll always get to you .
Jamie , Jamie , listen .
Today , in the cemetery , somebody dug up a coffin .
It was the coffin of a nine-year-old girl .
What do you think he 's going to do with that ?
Huh ?
You 're nine years old .
Aren 't you , Jamie ?
Dr. Loomis , leave the little girl alone .
Tears won 't get you anywhere . [ chuckles ]
Help me to find him ?
We 'll find him together .
There 's a reason why he has this power over you .
Did you ever wonder what it is ?
Baby .
[ bus rumbling ]
[ indistinct chattering ]
[ brakes squeaking ]
[ man ] Excuse me ,
where 's it supposed to stop before Chicago ?
[ driver ] Oh , let 's see , we 're gonna go to Bloomington ,
Redfield , Evanston , and our final destination .
[ dog yelps ]
- [ birds chirping ] - [ wind blowing ]
[ ominous music ]
- [ door clicks ] - [ door creaking ]
[ door bangs ]
[ floorboards creaking ]
Michael ?
[ wood creaking ]
Have you come home , Michael ?
I know what you want from her .
[ cane clattering ]
[ door creaking ]
[ ominous music ]
[ boots clanging ]
[ switch clicking ]
[ wood creaking ]
- [ metal thudding ] - [ suspenseful music ]
[ Loomis gasping ]
[ rat squeaking ]
[ Loomis laughs ]
[ metal creaking ]
- [ indistinct chattering ] - [ rock music playing on car radio ]
[ Tina laughing ]
♪ Steal your heart and I steal your cash
♪ I steal your car and you 'll get it back crashed ♪
♪ I said , baby , I 'm yours to punish if you 're mad ♪
♪ But what could you do ♪
♪ That I ain 't already had ♪
[ Tina shouts , laughs ]
Don 't you like the mask just a little bit ? [ shouts ]
Yeah , maybe you don 't even need to wear a mask , baby . [ giggles ]
♪ Then I tear out your heart ♪
♪ And let the devil in ♪
[ Tina singing along ] ♪ Baby I 'm yours , sha , la , la , la ♪
[ Spitz singing along ] ♪ Baby , I 'm ready , sha , la , la ♪
Ow . Bruised , but ready .
Hi .
[ siren wailing ]
♪ I 'm not your woman , you 're not my man ♪
Friends of yours ?
♪ I 'm not your girl ♪
♪ I 'm not your friend ♪
So , how many cases can we get ?
Three cases . Any more and I think old Mr. Casey
would , uh , know something 's up .
Hey , but we gotta get going . Shift change is pretty soon .
You gonna pull around back ,
or should we both just get busted out front ?
Oh , Mike .
Nice wax job .
Touch the car again and you 're dead .
- Okay ? - Okay .
Thank you .
You 're gonna get high blood pressure , Mikey .
Pick me up at eight at Rachel 's , okay ?
We gotta get ready for the Tower Farm party .
Hey , Mikey , wanna go have your legs waxed ? [ laughs ]
- [ car engine roaring ] - [ tires screeching ]
[ car engine revving ]
All right , that 's it , now , go , go , go .
And don 't - - don 't drink it all before we get there , okay ?
[ trunk bangs ]
Idiot .
[ car door clicks ]
[ car door bangs ]
[ Mike chuckles ]
[ rake thuds ]
- [ metal screeching ] - [ ominous music ]
What the ?
Okay , asshole .
You wanna play ?
Trick or trea - -
[ choking ]
[ crowbar clangs ]
- [ rake thuds ] - [ Mike groans ]
[ Mike groaning ]
[ man ] Three , two , one . Can you hear me out there ?
Testing , one , two , three .
[ indistinct chattering ]
[ microphone squeaking ]
[ bright piano music ]
Ooh , my , aren 't you pretty ?
Huh ?
Ooh .
These are for you .
Ooh , aren 't they beautiful , huh ?
We 'll have to put them in water .
It ... it 's good luck .
[ children laughing ]
First of all , I 'd like to thank you parents
for supporting us tonight .
Now , what we all been waiting for ,
our annual Halloween costume pageant .
Our first couple is Jenny Hogle and Kristin McGibb .
- Give ' em a big hand . - [ bright piano music ]
- [ insects chirping ] - [ ominous music ]
[ indistinct chattering ]
[ car engine roaring ]
- [ tires screeching ] - [ horn honking ]
[ heavy breathing ]
[ gloves creaking ]
[ door clicks ]
- [ door creaking ] - [ door thuds ]
[ ominous music ]
[ announcer ] Next is Tony Larkin and Diane Willis .
Jamie , come on .
[ heavy breathing ]
Tina , queen of room service . [ laughs ]
Michael , open the door .
Mike .
Michael , it 's cold out here .
Come on , open the door .
Mikey , ooh .
Mikey .
- [ ominous music ] - [ lock clicks ]
Thank you for being such a gentleman .
[ announcer ] And now , we have Billy Hill
and Jamie Carruthers .
[ laughs ] You 're wearing my present .
I want you to know I just love barbaric men .
[ gloves creaking ]
[ ominous music ]
... Jamie as a princess .
Give ' em a big hand .
Jamie , Jamie , what 's wrong ? Jamie , come on .
Michael , don 't I even get a kiss ?
[ Tina laughs ]
Well , I can 't resist your new look .
[ Billy ] Jamie , come on .
[ ominous music ]
It feels creepy .
[ gloves creaking ]
[ indistinct chattering ]
[ Jamie panting ]
[ Billy ] Jamie .
- [ audience gasps ] - [ Jamie screaming ]
- [ car engine roaring ] - [ tires screeching ]
[ group screaming ]
Jamie !
Jamie .
- [ car engine roaring ] - [ ominous music ]
[ boots clanging ]
Just great , the old silent treatment , huh , Mike ?
What 'd I do wrong this time , huh ?
Is it because I wanna see Jamie ?
Nothing , Mike .
That 's what I get , nothing .
Stop here , I want a pack of cigarettes .
[ car engine roars ]
I said stop the goddamn car .
I want a pack of cigarettes .
[ tires screeching ]
Come on , well ?
[ car engine roaring ]
Great . Psycho boyfriend .
[ indistinct chattering ]
- [ car door bangs ] - [ heavy breathing ]
- [ Jamie panting ] - Jamie , Tina is - - is she in danger ?
- Where is she ? - No , we 've gotta get her out of here .
Where is she ?
Tina , where is she , Jamie ?
[ group cheering ]
[ Jamie gasping ]
Jamie , you 've got to help us .
Get Meeker on the line .
Sergeant Meeker , what 's your 207 ?
[ groaning ]
Store .
- [ Jamie gasping ] - Store ?
[ Jamie grunting ]
What kind of store ? What do they sell there ?
[ grunting ] All-nighter .
All-nighter .
[ Jamie groaning ]
[ Loomis ] Yes ?
What do they , what do they sell ?
[ Billy and Jamie ] Big .
- Wo - - - [ Billy ] Woman .
A big woman ? A big woman who works ...
- works in the store , eh ? - No !
- [ Loomis ] What ? Jamie , what ? - [ Jamie sobbing ]
Cookie woman !
Cookie wo-woman .
Cookie woman ?
- [ Jamie panting ] - Cookie woman ?
Dale 's Gas Station , Fifth and Main .
[ ominous music ]
[ heavy breathing ]
[ sirens wailing ]
[ officer over speaker ] Tina Williams .
If you are Tina Williams , stay where you are .
[ tires screeching ]
[ police radio chattering ]
Great , check , check the inside .
[ officer over radio ] She appears unharmed .
[ Tina over radio ] What the hell is going on ? I 'm fine !
Please , you 've got to come with us to the clinic .
Is Jamie all right ?
Just get in the car .
[ officer ] Let 's get a car on either end of the street .
We 're bringing her in .
- [ ominous music ] - [ police radio chattering ]
- I don 't believe this . - Come on .
[ police radio chattering ]
[ officer ] Our ETA is 20 minutes .
[ indistinct chattering ]
Tina !
Where 's Jamie ? Is something wrong ?
Tina .
[ gentle pensive music ]
[ Jamie sighing ]
Say it again .
Tina .
I love it !
- [ Jamie ] Tina , don 't go . - I have to .
- Why ? - Because .
You might not understand , but [ sighs ]
when you 're older , there are people
you 're gonna meet who make you feel , like , connected ,
like your heart is made of neon .
And when you find them , you have to be with them .
But he was with you .
Who ?
The boogeyman .
Oh , yeah , that 's one way of describing him .
Tina , no !
Honey , I will come back later tonight ,
and I will sleep with you right here .
Tina !
I 'll be back . I love you .
[ ominous music ]
[ indistinct chattering ]
Why don 't you stay the night ?
Oh , I 'm sorry , I gotta run .
Tina , please .
Stay away , okay . You know , you 're really creepy
filling that little girl with all that boogeyman crap .
I believe that you 're in danger .
Jamie believes it , too .
Jamie 's a nine-year-old girl .
Be sensible .
[ Tina laughs ]
I 'm never sensible if I can help it .
- Hee , hee , hee ! - [ Loomis ] Tina !
For God 's sake , stop her .
- On whose orders ? - She hasn 't done anything wrong .
[ brooding music ]
Follow her , then .
At least you can do that .
If that girl dies tonight ...
All right , all right . For you , Doc , anything .
[ insects chirping ]
[ door bangs ]
You guys supposed to be trailing me or something ?
Well , then you can give me a ride to the Tower Farm .
[ ominous music ]
[ police radio chattering ]
[ whispering ] Tina . Gotta help Tina .
[ boots clanging ]
Jamie 's not in her room .
She 's nowhere in sight .
[ girl laughing ]
Hey ! [ screams ]
Loomis , what the hell are you doing ?
Jamie 's gone .
[ mask thuds ]
Oh , no .
[ footsteps tapping ]
- [ suspenseful music ] - [ both screaming ]
I 've gotta find Tina .
You don 't even know where she is .
But I do .
Where ?
The Tower Farm .
- [ upbeat rock music ] - [ indistinct chattering ]
- Love your costume . - Oh , baby .
[ music continues ]
Tina .
- What ? - Where 's Mike ?
Oh , ask me if I care .
[ insects chirping ]
What are you doing , huh ?
- What are you doing ? - Got a little thing here .
[ car engine roaring ]
[ ominous piano music ]
[ tires screeching ]
[ metal clanging ]
What do you think ?
Well , orders are orders .
That look like a life-threatening situation to you ?
Nah .
Play Crazy Eights ?
- [ muffled upbeat music ] - [ indistinct chattering ]
[ heavy breathing ]
♪ We 're not like an old book ♪
♪ That you read and put away ♪
♪ A story never ending ♪
♪ Don 't push our love away ♪
♪ Holding on to our dreams ♪
♪ Remembering what was true ♪
♪ Looking for something ♪
♪ For me or for you ♪
♪ Don 't give up just keep ... ♪
Spitz and I just had the greatest idea .
Yeah , what ?
♪ Together for so long ♪
[ both laughing ]
Let 's go .
- [ insects chirping ] - [ cards thudding ]
- [ both laughing ] - [ Tom ] No way , aw , no way !
- Hey , you cheated ! - [ Nick ] I did not cheat .
- Come on . - [ Sam screaming ]
- [ Nick ] I did not cheat . - [ Tom ] Jesus , what the ?
- [ Sam screaming ] - [ suspenseful music ]
[ car doors opening ]
[ Tina ] Take me , but spare my friend !
She 's a virgin .
[ Spitz ] Got her phone number ?
- [ laughs ] - [ screams ]
You think that 's funny ?
Hey , hey , no , no , no , man .
No , hey , it 's just a little Halloween prank , okay ?
Definitely not funny !
Somebody could easily be dead right now !
Fortunately , we 're lousy cops .
- [ grunts ] - Sorry .
- [ cat meowing ] - Hey , guys !
Hey .
Look what I found ! [ laughs ]
[ kitten meows ]
[ Tina and Spitz screaming ]
[ Spitz laughing ]
[ door creaking ]
[ door thuds ]
[ dog barking in distance ]
- [ Spitz ] Boo ! - [ both scream ]
- [ Spitz laughs ] - [ door creaking ]
[ Spitz chuckles ]
[ kitten meows ]
[ gasps ] Oh , more kittens !
Oh , look at ' em .
- [ kitten meows ] - Hello , hello , little kittens .
- Hello . - Oh , they 're so cute .
Aw . Oh .
Get ' em , Tina , get ' em , Tina , get ' em , get ' em .
You , you , you , wait , wait , wait .
Kisses for the kitten .
- [ ominous music ] - [ door creaking ]
[ door thuds ]
Little wee cat ?
Kitten ?
[ kissing noises ]
[ heavy breathing ]
[ Tina ] Psst , kitten .
I 'm coming to get you . [ laughs ]
[ Tina gasps ]
[ door creaking ]
[ door thuds ]
Kitten ? [ gasps ]
- [ ominous music ] - [ kitten meows ]
[ heavy breathing ]
[ kitten meowing ]
Kitten , I hear you , but I don 't see you .
[ wood creaking ]
[ kitten meows ]
- [ suspenseful music ] - [ kitten yowling ]
[ kitten meowing ]
[ wood creaking ]
Oh , my God . [ sighs ]
[ kitten meowing ]
- [ metal thudding ] - [ ominous music ]
[ straw crunching ]
- [ cat meows ] - [ Tina gasps ]
[ laughs ] What am I doing ?
I hate cats .
- Oh . - [ door creaking ]
Sam ?
Sammy ?
Spitz ?
[ wood creaking ]
- [ Tina gasps ] - [ ominous music ]
- [ suspenseful music ] - [ Tina screams ]
[ Spitz laughing ]
Oh , God !
I hate you !
Oh , sorry .
- God ! - Did you see her face ?
You guys .
- [ Spitz ] That was great . - [ wood creaking ]
[ Spitz and Tina laughing ]
Fine , I 'll just let myself out .
- Bye . - [ Spitz ] I 'll be right back .
[ laughing ]
[ cat meows ]
- Have fun . - Okay .
- Whee ! - Whoo ! [ laughs ]
- [ kitten meowing ] - [ door creaking ]
[ Sam laughs ]
Spitz ?
What makes you think I 'm gonna try and find you , huh ?
[ wood cracking ]
[ Sam laughs ]
[ wood creaking ]
I got you !
- [ door creaking ] - [ ominous music ]
I saw you , ooh !
[ door creaking ]
[ door bangs ]
- [ straw crunching ] - [ wood creaking ]
Spitz , I 'm out of here !
Good night !
Ouch !
- [ Sam giggles ] - [ body thuds ]
Spitz .
Oh , my God !
- [ Sam screaming ] - [ suspenseful music ]
[ Spitz laughing ]
You son of a bitch ! You scared me half to death !
- Ow , ow , ow ! - That wasn 't funny !
Ruff . [ laughing ]
Whoo ! Ruff !
[ police radio chattering ]
[ dog barking in distance ]
[ Sam laughs ]
[ wood creaking ]
- [ Sam laughs ] - [ wood creaking ]
[ Sam giggling ]
[ Spitz growls ]
[ wood creaking ]
[ Spitz moans ]
- [ Sam moaning ] - [ wood creaking ]
[ Spitz moaning ]
[ Sam moans ]
- [ Sam moans ] - [ wood creaking ]
Spitz , no .
- Spitz - - - What , what ?
- [ Sam ] No . - What 's the matter ?
Spitz , I don 't have anything . [ laughs ]
[ Sam giggles ]
[ wood creaking ]
- [ wood creaking ] - [ heavy breathing ]
[ ominous music ]
[ metal scraping ]
[ Sam moaning ]
[ wood creaking ]
- [ suspenseful music ] - [ Spitz groans ]
[ Sam screaming ]
[ Spitz groaning ]
[ body thuds ]
[ Sam crying ]
- [ Sam screaming ] - [ door thuds ]
You son of a bitch !
Ah !
- [ Sam screams ] - [ pitchfork thuds ]
- [ blade whooshes ] - [ Sam shouts ]
[ insects chirping ]
That sounded different .
[ chuckles ] We never did stuff like that when we were kids .
No , we were normal .
Yeah .
[ rock music playing indistinctly ]
Hey , fella ! Over here !
Hey , come on . Enough 's enough , all right ?
Yeah , somebody can get hurt with that thing .
Hey , somebody 's gonna get hurt with that thing .
Unbelievable . No respect for authority anymore .
- It 's the parents . - Yeah .
Hey . All right , punk , I 'm through fooling around .
- [ music continues ] - [ indistinct chattering ]
♪ I love that sound ♪
So , you coming to the spring ?
Oh , baby , you just wanna see me naked .
- [ boy ] I wouldn 't mind . - [ Tina laughs ]
Come on , the hell with Mike . He ain 't gonna show .
I can 't leave Sam and Spitz .
♪ Up and down , yeah , yeah ♪
- [ group cheering ] - [ engines revving ]
- [ car horn honking ] - [ indistinct chattering ]
[ insects chirping ]
Hurry , come on .
- [ engines roaring ] - [ car horn honking ]
[ indistinct chattering ]
[ wood creaking ]
Sam .
You guys ?
You guys , I don 't hear any noise .
Are you sure you 're doing it right ?
[ wood creaking ]
You guys wanna come skinny-dipping ?
[ Jamie and Billy panting ]
Maybe you guys are already naked .
[ wood creaking ]
- Oh , God . - [ ominous music ]
[ kitten meows ]
Oh , my God .
[ gasps ] Oh !
- [ suspenseful music ] - [ Tina screaming ]
Oh , God ! Help me !
Help me , please !
Somebody help me !
Please help me !
Stop !
Oh , God .
Help me . Please , help me .
Help me .
[ suspenseful music ]
Oh ! [ whimpering ]
Mike .
Tina !
- [ suspenseful music ] - [ Tina screams ]
[ Tina screaming ]
Tina !
[ car engine roaring ]
- [ boards crashing ] - [ Tina screaming ]
Leave her alone !
[ Tina screaming ]
What do you want ?
[ tires screeching ]
[ Tina gasps ]
Leave her !
- No . - Here , here !
- [ Halloween theme music ] - [ car engine roaring ]
Billy !
No !
Billy ! No !
[ car engine roaring ]
Please !
No ! Please !
[ trees thudding ]
Please !
[ Jamie screams ]
No !
Please !
Stay here , Billy . I 'll be back .
[ Jamie screaming ]
Leave her alone !
Oh , my God !
[ Jamie ] No , please !
Jamie !
[ Jamie screaming ]
Help me !
Leave me alone !
Stop !
Stop , Jamie !
No , no !
No !
[ Jamie screaming ]
[ explosion booming ]
[ horn wailing ]
[ Tina screams ]
[ fire crackling ]
[ sobbing ]
[ horn continues blaring ]
[ Billy gasping ]
[ Jamie ] Tina .
Baby .
Tina .
Tina !
[ car horn stops ]
[ Jamie coughs ]
[ metal creaking ]
[ ominous music ]
[ suspenseful music ]
[ Halloween theme music ]
[ whimpers ]
No !
Oh , God !
Ow !
[ Jamie groaning ]
No !
Ow !
[ Jamie yells ]
[ Jamie groaning ]
No , no !
No !
[ Tina ] Jamie !
[ Jamie and Tina screaming ]
No !
Run ! [ whimpering ]
- [ knife thuds ] - [ Tina groaning ]
No !
- [ Tina ] Run ! - No !
- [ Tina ] Run ! - Tina !
- Come on . - No , Tina !
No !
Run .
Tina !
- [ Tina ] Run . - [ Jamie ] Please , Tina !
[ Billy ] Come on .
[ Jamie crying ]
Tina !
Tina .
[ ominous music ]
Please .
- [ suspenseful music ] - [ Jamie screams ]
Tina . [ whimpering ]
[ man ] All right , spread out and keep in contact .
- Where did they go ? - [ Loomis ] Don 't shoot !
[ man ] There 's two of them , right here !
- [ officer ] Loomis . - [ Loomis ] Yeah , I got them here .
Jamie , come on . Get them out of here .
- All right . - Spread out , find the other girl .
[ man 2 ] Where 's the other one ?
Come on , Loomis .
- [ man 3 ] One is still missing . - [ man 4 ] The other girl 's still missing .
- Move out , find the other girl . - [ man 5 ] Watch yourself .
It 's all right . It 's gonna be all right .
Jamie , it 's gonna be all right .
Tina , please .
[ police radio chattering ]
[ Jamie ] Tina !
Tina !
Tina .
All right , put three units over at the reservoir and let me know when ...
Now are you willing to help me ?
Can you kill him ?
- I think so . - Now , wait a minute , Loomis .
There isn 't a minute to wait .
What do you want me to do ?
[ car engines humming ]
[ insects chirping ]
[ ominous music ]
Michael .
It will destroy you , too ,
one day , Michael ,
this rage which drives you .
You think if you kill them all , it will go away .
It won 't .
You have to fight it in the place where it 's strongest .
Where it all began .
If you want to get rid of this rage ,
Michael , go home .
Go home !
Go to your house .
I shall be there waiting for you .
You 'll find her waiting for you .
[ music continues ]
[ Jamie sighs ]
[ leaves rustling ]
Can he see us from the street ?
[ man ] Not a chance .
Station one , are you sure he can 't see you ?
[ static buzzes ]
[ Meeker over radio ] Inside units , I want a report every five minutes .
Roger .
10-4 .
We may not be able to see you , Sheriff ,
but we can all certainly hear you .
All right , relax , Loomis . This is my operation .
All right , fellas , let 's keep it down on the radio chatter .
[ static buzzes ]
[ officer ] Looks like you and me are the only ones around here
keeping our cool .
Shh .
[ officer whispers ] Good idea .
You wanna practice our signals ?
All right .
[ brush tapping ]
You do that good and loud , I 'll be out here in a flash .
You 're one brave little girl .
[ Jamie panting ]
Bill - - Billy .
Billy !
B-Billy . [ panting ]
[ officer ] Dr. Loomis ?
B-Billy .
Dr. Loomis ?
Billy .
Meeker , he 's at the clinic .
[ Jamie ] B-Billy .
[ man ] This is car 16 calling the Masterson Clinic .
Car 16 calling the Masterson Clinic .
We just had a distress call from the clinic .
They haven 't been able to reach ' em again .
There were four men up there .
All right , this is Sheriff Meeker .
All mobile units ,
proceed immediately to the Masterson Clinic .
- [ indistinct chattering ] - [ car engine starting ]
- [ siren wailing ] - All right , move out , move out .
[ indistinct chattering ]
[ Meeker ] Come on , get going !
[ man ] Stop dragging your ass ! Move , move it , move it !
All right , you stay here . Loomis , I 'm moving the girl
to the police station . She 'll be safer there .
Understood .
[ Meeker ] Move it out .
- Let 's go . - We 're all clear .
The girl , Charlie , and Loomis are in there still .
- [ engine revving ] - All right , I got it .
- [ police radio chattering ] - [ sirens wailing ]
[ radio thuds ]
[ door clicks ]
Now you 'll come , won 't you , Michael ?
[ ominous music ]
I 'd say you 've done your night 's work .
Come on , my pal , Eddy and I 'll give you a ride to the station .
Let 's go .
[ door opens ]
[ Charlie ] Dr. Loomis .
[ lock clicks ]
What the hell are you doing ?
We aren 't taking her anywhere .
You 've got five seconds to give me that key before I take it .
[ ominous music ]
Charlie , can you read me ?
This is Charlie . What 's going on ?
- [ tires screeching ] - [ Eddy ] There 's a car approaching .
I 'll check it out .
Looks like one of ours .
It 's a code two .
Hey - - [ Eddy groans ]
Eddy , do you read me ?
[ Jamie panting ]
- [ glass shattering ] - [ Eddy groaning ]
- [ ominous music ] - [ Charlie ] Eddy , can you read me ?
[ Eddy screaming over radio ]
- [ head thudding ] - [ Eddy groaning ]
- Eddy , come in ! - [ Eddy screaming over radio ]
Oh , Christ , I 've got to call Meeker .
- [ Jamie gasps ] - [ radio thudding ]
You crazy son of a bitch !
[ gun clicks ]
Charlie .
Charlie , Michael Myers is outside .
Stay with the little girl .
Please ?
[ lock clicking ]
I 'm so sorry .
Don 't worry about this .
- [ heavy breathing ] - [ ominous music ]
[ board thudding ]
- [ ominous music ] - [ heavy breathing ]
We have to get out of here .
[ ominous music ]
You 've ... you 've come back to us , Michael .
I - --
I know why you 've come back , Michael .
Because the little girl ...
the little girl can stop the rage inside .
She knows how to do it , Michael , if - - if you let her .
She can stop the rage ...
the rage inside .
Oh , she 's not up there , Michael .
She 's down here in the middle of the old house .
[ Loomis chuckles ]
Your house , Michael .
Your house .
Don 't you remember how much better you used to be ?
Let - - let me take you .
Let me take you to her .
She 'll take your rage away .
Michael , you 'll be ...
better then .
You don 't need ...
you don 't need that .
- [ suspenseful music ] - [ Loomis groaning ]
- [ Loomis screaming ] - [ glass shattering ]
- [ wood thudding ] - [ Loomis groaning ]
[ glass shattering ]
[ Jamie screams ]
Hurry !
Please !
[ dramatic music ]
[ Jamie ] Hurry !
- Don 't worry about it . - Please .
- [ boards snapping ] - Oh !
All right , let me get this out the window .
Step over it .
All right .
I need you on my back here .
Now you just hold on .
[ Jamie whimpering ]
[ knife thuds ]
All right .
[ wood cracking ]
[ gun firing ]
All right .
Come on .
- [ wood thudding ] - [ suspenseful music ]
[ fist thudding ] [ Charlie groaning ]
[ board thuds ]
[ Halloween theme music ]
[ Charlie groaning ]
- [ Eddy shouts ] - [ neck snaps ]
[ indistinct chattering , shouting ]
Hold it .
Oh , my God .
Damn it .
All right , when everybody 's out , I want a sweep of the building and grounds .
[ man over radio ] Sheriff Meeker , do you copy ?
- Yeah . - [ man ] Third floor 's secure .
Moving on to second .
- All right , keep it up ! - [ siren wailing ]
- [ door bangs ] - [ lock clicking ]
[ ominous music ]
[ lock clicking ]
- [ wood creaking ] - [ footsteps tapping ]
No , no .
[ door clangs ]
[ door banging ]
- [ door bangs ] - [ door creaking ]
Please don 't let him get me .
Please , God .
[ ominous piano music ]
[ heavy breathing ]
[ Jamie whimpering ] No .
[ door clanging ]
[ Jamie grunting ]
[ suspenseful music ]
[ Jamie screaming ]
[ body thuds ]
- [ heavy breathing ] - [ footsteps tapping ]
[ Jamie whimpering ]
- [ ominous music ] - [ metal squeaking ]
[ Jamie grunting ]
- [ metal squeaking ] - [ Jamie yells ]
- [ knife clanging ] - [ Jamie screaming ]
[ Jamie screaming ]
[ Jamie grunting ]
- [ metal clanging ] - [ Jamie screaming ]
[ Jamie crying ]
[ Jamie cries ]
- [ knife clanging ] - [ Jamie screaming ]
[ suspenseful music ]
[ Jamie grunting ]
[ ominous music ]
[ sirens wailing ]
[ Jamie whimpering ]
Oh , God !
- [ Jamie panting ] - [ door handle jiggling ]
[ hand pounding ]
[ ominous music ]
[ wood creaking ]
[ flames crackling ]
[ wings fluttering ]
[ wood creaking ]
- [ dog barks ] - Max !
[ suspenseful music ]
[ Jamie screams ]
No !
Rachel !
No ! [ crying ]
- [ ominous music ] - [ footsteps tapping ]
Rachel .
[ wood creaking ]
Help me , help me .
Uncle .
Boogeyman .
[ heavy breathing ]
Let me see .
[ gentle ominous music ]
You 're just like me .
Let me .
[ wood creaking ]
- [ Jamie gasps ] - [ suspenseful music ]
[ Jamie screams ]
[ boards thudding ]
[ Halloween theme music ]
[ Jamie screaming ]
Oh , God !
You want her ?
- No ! - Here she is !
[ Jamie whimpers ]
[ Loomis ] Here 's your ...
- No ! - ... your little girl .
No !
- No , no ! - Come and get her !
[ Jamie ] Please !
- [ Loomis ] Come and - - - [ Jamie ] No !
- No , please ! - Come and get your - -
- No ! - ... little girl !
No !
- Come take us both ! - No !
Michael , let 's play a game .
No !
Catch the little girl .
Come , come catch her .
- [ Jamie ] No ! - [ Loomis ] Michael .
No .
Get the little girl , then - - then you 're home and safe .
[ chain clanging ]
[ chain thuds ]
[ ominous music ]
- [ gun fires ] - [ chains clanging ]
[ gun clicks ]
- [ gun fires ] - [ Jamie screaming ]
- [ gun firing ] - [ Jamie screaming ]
- [ Loomis gasps ] - [ gun thuds ]
[ board creaking ]
- [ Loomis grunts ] - [ board whooshes ]
- [ Loomis grunts ] - [ board thudding ]
Die , die , die , die !
Michael !
Die !
Die , die !
[ board thuds ]
[ body thuds ]
[ Jamie crying ]
- [ body thuds ] - [ Loomis groaning ]
[ insects chirping ]
[ sirens wailing in distance ]
[ brooding music ]
[ Jamie crying ]
[ tires screeching ]
[ indistinct chattering ]
The National Guard will take him to a maximum security facility
where he 'll stay till the day he dies .
He 'll never die .
All right , take her back to the clinic .
Come on .
[ ominous music ]
[ insects chirping ]
[ boots clanging ]
[ man ] Okay , Tony , I 'll see you in the morning , huh ?
- Good job . - [ Tony ] All right . Take care , Joe .
Thanks .
Hey , Joe ?
[ Joe ] Yeah ?
[ Ton ] Don 't forget , you said you 'd cover for me tomorrow .
[ Joe ] Yeah , I got it . Don 't worry about it .
Take it easy !
[ man ] Hey , you said you were gonna cover for me , too !
[ Joe ] Get out of here .
[ explosion booming ]
[ ominous music ]
- [ guns firing ] - [ man ] Get him !
- [ man 2 ] Get your weapons ! - [ man 3 ] I can 't !
- [ man ] Spread out ! - [ guns firing ]
- Wait in the car . - [ gun firing ]
[ indistinct shouting ]
[ man screaming ]
[ music continues ]
[ Jamie whimpering ]
[ fire crackling ]
No .
No ! [ voice echoing ]
[ Halloween theme music ]
[ ominous music ]